<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Create a new Motwin Request Processor">
   <intro>
      <description>
      This cheat sheet shows you how to create a simple Motwin Request Processor.
<br/><br/>
Pre-requisites:
<br/>- having a Motwin server application project created
<br/>- having a Spring beans definition file with the Motwin namespaces declared. Such a file is created thanks to the New Motwin Server project wizard.  
<br/><br/>
Make sure you use the <b>exact values</b> indicated in the cheat sheet scenario. Otherwise, you may not be able to use automatic actions provided in the cheat sheet.
<br/><br/>
Don&apos;t forget to check each step before going to the next one. 
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Open the Spring Bean Definition file">
      <description>
         Open the Spring Bean Definition file (by default, the one generated with the New Motwin Server Project is named <b>application.xml</b>) with the Spring Config Editor (usually this is the default editor).
         <br/>This should open an Editor with several tabs:
         <br/>- Source
         <br/>- Namespaces
         <br/>- Overview
         <br/>- beans
         <br/>- Motwin Channel
         <br/>- Motwin Messaging
         <br/>- <b>Motwin Requesting</b>
         <br/>- ...
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Select the Motwin Requesting tab">
      <description>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Click New Processor button">
   	  <description>
   	  	Click the <b>&quot;New Processor&quot;</b> button: this opens a form to create a new Requesting Processor.
   	  </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Declare the message type">
   	  <description>
   	  	Enter the type of message handled by the processor in the <b>type*</b> field (for instance, &quot;hello&quot;).
   	  </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Click the class link" dialog="true">
   	  <description>
   	  	Click the <b>&quot;class&quot;</b> link to create a new request processor and fill in the wizard.
   	  </description>
   	  <onCompletion>
   	  That's it, you've created a Request Processor!
   	  <br/>
   	  <br/>Implement <b>processRequest</b> method to define how to handle incoming request. This method will be invoked when receiving a Request of the specified type from a remote device. Response must be set within this method.
   	  </onCompletion>
   	  <subitem label="Enter a package name or select an existing one">
   	  </subitem>
   	  <subitem label="Enter the class name of the Request Processor (for instance &quot;MyRequestProcessor&quot;)">
   	  </subitem>
   	  <subitem label="In the Interfaces field, modify the generic parameters &lt;Object,Object&gt; of the interface &quot;com.motwin.sdk.application.messaging.MessageProcessor&quot; with your domain POJOs. The first generic parameter is the POJO handled by the message request; the second generic parameter is the POJO handled by the message response."
   	  		   skip="true">
   	  </subitem>
   	  <subitem label="Click &quot;Finish&quot;.">
   	  </subitem>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>